http://www.collegian.psu.edu/site/privacy.html

State College, PA
(16801)
Today
Intervals of clouds and sunshine. High 52F. Winds light and variable..
Tonight
Partly to mostly cloudy. Low 32F. Winds light and variable.
Subscribe
Effective date Feb. 11, 2010. Updated on March 22, 2018.OverviewCollegian Inc. owns and operates a Web site known as The Daily Collegian Online ("our site"). The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available and operated under the domain(s) and/or subdomain(s) of www.collegian.psu.edu and www.psucollegian.com. By visiting our site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, do not use or access our site. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information our site gathers about visitors and the ways in which we use and don't use that information.By accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy through accessing the services provided, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.We reserve the right to amend or modify our Privacy Policy at any time in the future, in which case we will post a revised Privacy Policy on our site and update the Effective Date to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use our site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified. Therefore, you should check periodically for an updated policy. All amended terms are automatically effective once they are posted on our site.This Privacy Policy applies solely to The Daily Collegian Online and does not cover any other activities or services, including print publishing, undertaken by Collegian Inc. About Third Party AdvertisingWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our Services. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our sites or use of our Services and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message).We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's (https://www.networkadvertising.org/) consumer website.Google Doubleclick for Publishers (DFP) is an ad network partner that displays ads on our Services. To improve your ad experience on our sites and Services and elsewhere on the Internet, we may send non-personal information to Google DFP based on your browser's activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see is relevant to you. Google DFP also may use information regarding its own users to select which ads to display. To learn more about Google DFP's ad practices, including how to opt out of using anonymous information to select which ads to show you -- visit https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ Opt-Out of CookiesIf you wish to manage or opt-out of cookies utilized by our site and third party advertisers, you can take the following steps:You may be able to download an opt-out cookie from the third party advertiser's website allowing you to opt-out of cookies. Please visit the third party advertiser's websites for more information.Your web browser may allow you to manage what cookies are accepted or declined. These settings can usually be found in the preferences or options menus of your web browser.Your web browser may also allow you to manually view cookies and delete the cookies you don't want or need. Check your web browser's settings for more information.Websites that require registration may allow you to opt-out of cookies. Check the account settings or preferences section of the website for more information.For more information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. Information that is automatically gatheredDuring normal Web browsing, our site automatically logs information based on your behavior on the site, which may include:(1.) The URL that you just came from and to which URL you go next.(2.) Your Internet Protocol (IP) address.(3.) The date, time and length of time of your visit.(4.) Any page you visited.(5.) Your computer operating system and browser type and version (if provided by the browser).(6.) Search words you use to search our site.The information collected does not identify you by name or any other personally identifiable fact. The information is used in aggregate form for internal reporting and marketing purposes. For example, we publicly release how many visitors our site receives on a monthly basis.Collegian Inc. reserves the right to use client- or server-based cookies or "Web beacons" to track activity on our site and enhance traffic statistical information. However, companies that display ads or provide services on our site may use cookings or other tracking mechanisms. Their use of these technologies is governed by their privacy policies. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist the service provider in developing and providing its services.Collegian Inc. occasionally offers services provided by external third parties to provide linked services for visitors of Web sites operated by Collegian Inc. The privacy policy of the external third party applies, not our Privacy Policy. If you visit one of these linked sites or a Collegian Web page that uses an external organization's services, you should first review that organization's privacy policy and its other policies.Collegian Inc. is not responsible in any way for the content or policies of other organizations, and cannot protect information you provide directly to a linked site or service.Collegian Inc. cannot protect you from unlawful interception by third parties.Collegian Inc. reserves the right to and may add, change and/or delete additional third-party providers for The Daily Collegian Online from time to time at any time without notice.Information provided by usersThe Daily Collegian Online does not require any type of registration for normal browsing. However, we do sometimes request personal information for specific purposes, such as verifying a letter to the editor or posting a comment on a blog.When we do collect personal information, Collegian Inc. will use it only for the purpose for which we requested it. We do not sell or distribute personally identifiable information to third parties except where required by law. Collegian Inc. will cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, investigations, and requests and disclose any information, with or without a subpoena, that is needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request or assist in any investigation of a law enforcement agency.Our site is not directed to children younger than the age of 13 years, and we do not knowingly collect or distribute information from or about children younger than the age of 13 years.Your California privacy rightsThe California Civil Code gives California residents the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company disclosed personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if a company has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for use of your personal information by third parties for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure options.The Daily Collegian does not disclose personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Thus, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your personal information for marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year.
Support Student Journalism
Your contribution will help the Collegian provide award winning journalism to the Penn State community and beyond.
Donate to the Collegian by clicking the button below.
Latest Tweets
Tweets by @DailyCollegian
Newsletters
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
At a Glance
At a Glance--going through the highlights of the news so you don't have to. Sign up today!
Daily Collegian Sports
Get weekend previews and weekend recaps from The Daily Collegian Sports staff sent to your inbox.
You must select at least one email list.
Please enter a valid email address.
Sign up
Manage your lists
Latest Daily Collegian
The Daily Collegian for Nov. 19, 2020
Click to view the latest pdf edition.
more Daily Collegian Back Issues
Order your Finals Issue copy today!
Pick up! Take out!
Order from local restaurants here.
We can list the ordering and take out for your restaurant here.
Click here to send us your information.
McLanahan’s
Collegian Podcasts
PODCAST: We Are... Trying Our Best, Ep. 19: Holiday Special
PODCAST: Will Rutgers defeat Penn State football for the first time since 1988?
PODCAST: Friendly Neighborhood Podcast, Ep. 6: What should students do at home during the extended ‘break?’
PODCAST: We Are… Trying Our Best, Ep. 18: Thanksgiving Special
Featured Photo
Celebration, Lady Lions vs. Rams
Josie ChenUpdated
Dec 5, 2020
The celebration after winning 70-69 against Rhode Island Rams during a NCAA women’s basketball game in Bryce Jordan Center at Penn State on Thursday, Dec. 3, 2020.
Submit Your News
We're always interested in hearing about news in our community. Let us know what's going on!
Go to form
